veridiancu.org 2016-04-06

# 

                                                                                                                         Rev. 5/15
                        WHAT DOES VERIDIAN CREDIT UNION DO
FACTS                   WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                    Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                        consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we
                        collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand
                        what we do.
What?                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                        with us. This information can include:
                           Social Security number and account balances
                           account transactions and checking account information
                           credit history and credit scores
                        When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                        notice.
How?                    All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                        business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
                        personal information; the reasons Veridian Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can
                        limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                    Does Veridian Credit           Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                  Union share?
For our everyday business purposes –                                           Yes                                No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –                                                   Yes                                No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                             Yes                                No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                               Yes                                No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                               No                        We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                            No                        We don’t share
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                             No                        We don’t share
Questions?              Call toll-free (800) 235-3228 or go to www.veridiancu.org
                                                                                                       DIACV2 (DXPS01-E)

Page 2
What we do
How does Veridian Credit Union To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
protect my personal            security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
information?                   safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Veridian Credit Union We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal               open an account or use your credit or debit card
information?                      show your government-issued ID or apply for financing
                                  make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                               affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                  sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your
                                  creditworthiness
                                  affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                  sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               nonfinancial companies.
                                  Our affiliates include financial companies, such as Veridian Insurance; and
                                  nonfinancial companies, such as Veridian Fiscal Solutions.
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               nonfinancial companies.
                                  Veridian Credit Union does not share with our nonaffiliates so they can market to
                                  you.
Joint Marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                               financial products or services to you.
                                  Our joint marketing partners include financial advisors and insurance companies.
Other important information
